this is thinking outside the box bro
I will show you my resale plan
call it there
clean guy
clean showcase
barber chair or beauty salon
dog tour and hand over flyer
but all this
it's actually a big conveyor belt of expensive services
through this simple service
that anyone can do
you can increase your networking
just do it quickly
without dirt
closed beauty
have more opportunity then say hello
get my zap there man
tamo together
so bro
the strategy is clean showcases
to generate a connection with people to put
other products and services
and then I ride
an income within my own system
turned on
i wanted to know
if you would have a chance for me to put the truffles here
that's it
it's the same thing
it's mass
another commercial point here o
and here I have what
the so-called upsel
i can sell more stuff using
my own network
and on that same label here
i have a big plan
Trojan horse to put my resale to work
I conquered the territory
I create a self-sustaining plan and I start watering
my plantation
of truffles
would put here
so you only know something controlled
I take the money
I do what brother
I reinvest the profit
in that same tribe
when we get a product
which is already validated on the market
the product tends to sell faster
and that's where you get
in the brother turn
if you are not an immediate person
and know how to plant and then harvest
works the relationship
dominates the territory
make a label that does not depend only on the resale
will give you more freedom
that you can do other things brother
so let's put brother in the dough
call what's going on here
can be
I will pick it up then
if i have it there i do it now i will get conflict from Novo
go
thanks saw people
thank you
my dear
if you have patience
to wait for the fruits to grow you will reap fruits
ripe will reap the green fruit
will reap the green fruit
four points now
crazy at the convenience post
at a women's thrift store
in two barbershops
and as I speak to you here
oh i just got a pix my brother
to caraca
the thing is how you assemble your strategy to harvest
at the front
my brother
things are like that
doing other things
invest and will clean window
go get flyer
and that's my bro let's go Brother